{
    "id": "b33bcc487024473bb2c3e6c766bf1fe5",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Look",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "7e5d55247dd243c6817e53310804137c",
            "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Look",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who will look .............................. your pets when you are on holiday?",
                    "description": "To look after somebody is to take care of them.",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "of",
                        "after"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "If we have time we will have a look ............................... the city.",
                    "description": "To look around a place is to explore it",
                    "answers": [
                        "around",
                        "over",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will look ............................. all the applications before hiring someone.",
                    "description": "To look at something is to consider it or examine it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "at",
                        "up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is looking ............................. a hefty fine and jail term if he does not prove his innocence.",
                    "description": "To look at something is to face it or confront it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "for",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Tears roll down my cheeks, whenever I look ............................... on my childhood.",
                    "description": "To look back on something is to think about it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "back",
                        "up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "When they became rich they began to look ................................ their poor neighbors.",
                    "description": "To look down on somebody is to consider them inferior.",
                    "answers": [
                        "down",
                        "below",
                        "down on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Can you help me look ............................... my cat? She has been missing since morning.",
                    "description": "To look for somebody or something is to search for them or it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "out",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am really looking ............................... to becoming a mother.",
                    "description": "To look forward to something is to be excited about something that will happen in the future.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "forwards",
                        "forward"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Julie looked ................................... us on her way home.",
                    "description": "To look in on somebody is to pay them a short visit.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "in on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The supervisor has agreed to look ............................... the matter.",
                    "description": "To look into something is to investigate it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "up",
                        "into"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I looked ................................. as the children played in the park.",
                    "description": "To look on is to watch an activity without getting involved.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "on",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Look ..........................! The floor is wet.",
                    "description": "This is an expression used to warn someone to be careful.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "on",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}